Guide to the Anne Morrow Lindbergh Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional material, Circa 1929-1988; 1970-1985; Accession 1987-M-003
  - Correspondence from friends and acquaintances
    - Frelinghuysen, Peter, 1984 March 9 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Garrison, Lloyd, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Gow, Betty (Elizabeth Mowat), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Grandin, Ruth (Thompson), 1981 December 8 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Grelick, Donald and Robley, 1985 June 29 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Guggenheim, Dianne (Hamilton), 1983 June 12 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Gunney, Hilda, 1983 December 12 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Gunther, Jane, 1983 August 17 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Harris, Louisa, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Hatt, Robert T., Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Hatt, Sue (Vaillant), 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Henderson, Mary and Laubengayer, Karen, 1985 August 7 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Hill, Helen, 1983 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Hocking, Richard and Kay, 1981 February 11 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Hoguet, Susan, 1985 July 30, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Howell, Roselle, 1984 June 8 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Huber, Jack, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Hurd, Katrina, 1983 August 20 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Ide, Elizabeth, 1985 August 7 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Imlay, Jeanette (Greene), 1984 April 26 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Jenkins, James, 1981 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Jewett, Betty, 1981 February 24 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Jobst, Verne, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Kennan, George, 1975 November 2-December 12 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Krevel, Miriam, 1981 November 12 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Ladd, Laurel, 1983 August 1 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Lamb, Beatrice, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Lamb, Julia Flitner, 1980 December (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Lamont, Corliss, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Lanier, Jean, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Lefferts, Irene, 1975-1984 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Lewis, Shirley, 1983 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Lyden, Ruth, 1983 February 22-September 27 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Matthias, Blanche, 1982 June 17 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Maxwell, Emmy, 1983 October (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Maya, Enrique, 1981 October 15 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - McC[?], Marcia Bull, 1982 April 19, 1983 October 10 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - McGavin, Ann, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Medina, Beatrix, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Meissinger, Lilli and Vincent, Gertrude, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Miller, Pam, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Mitchell, Stephen, 1981 April 29-May 31 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Moreillon, Eglantine, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Morgan, Barbara, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Mutten, Cathy, 1981 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Mutten, Cathy, Gary and Shane, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Newton, Eleanor "Ellie" (Forde), 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Newton, James "Jim" Draper, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Obermer, Nesta, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Oldrin, John, 1980 October 23 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Omer, Patty, 1981 February 2-June 14 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Pecova (?), Ann, Undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Peppet, Rosemary, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Pfeiffer, Mara, 1984 January 8-August 5 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Philips, Sylvia, 1984 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Read, David Thurber, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Read, Frances, 1982 October 28 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Reading group, 1978-1981, undated (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Regina Laudis Monastery, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Rejamey, Anne, 1983 August 20 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Rice, Doug and Lynn, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Rich, Frank Hart, 1981 November 6 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Rodewald, Elizabeth, 1984 April 15 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Rosen, Hazel, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Rosen, Dr. John N., 1981 May 15 (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Saunders, Jean, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Schiff, Judith, 1985 March 25 (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Schley, Reeve, 1984 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Smith, Carleton, 1980-1988 (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - Smith, Elizabeth A. Marion, 1980 September 21 (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Smith, Frances Hayward, 1980 November 27 (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Steindl-Rast, Bro. David, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Stewart, Judy, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Stirling, Monica
      - 1973, 1980 November 27-1982 May 5 (Box 1, Folder 111-113)
      - 1982 May 19-1983 June 9 (Box 2, Folder 1-4)
    - Stohlman, Martha Lou, 1984 March 29 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Strudwick, Mary, 1981-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Swanson, Minnie, 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Tallinski, Madeleine, 1980 September 24-26 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Taquey, Charles H. and Kitty (McVitty), 1983 September 9 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Terry, Edith, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Thomas, Lowell, 1981 April 3 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Tomlinson, Meta, 1983 November 16 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Trask, Elsie (Barber), 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Trask, Jane, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Trippe, Betty, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Valentine, Lucia (Norton), 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Van Waes, Annemieke, 1980 October 15 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Waldenburger, Anne, 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Walter, Pam, Circa 1981-circa 1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Washburn, Brad, 1980 October 22 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Welch, G. Harold, 1983 February 18 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Wendt, Alice, Circa 1983-circa 1984 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Wheeler, Elsie (Trask), 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Williams, Susan, 1985 July 9-August 26 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Wolff, Helen, 1981-1985 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Wriggins, Howard and Sally, 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Wriggins, Sally, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - _____, Ana (Maria), 1981 September 4 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - _____, Garry, 1983 July 14 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - _____, Judy, 1981 December 30 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - _____, Lorian, 1982 February 4 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - _____, Luanne, 1984 April 28 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - _____, Nancy, 1982 February 9 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - _____, Painter, Circa 1981 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - _____, Sue, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Unidentified, 1981-1983, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Family correspondence
    - Brown, Marjory W., 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Brown, Reeve (Lindbergh), 1975-1984 (Box 2, Folder 38-39)
    - Feydy, Charles, 1975-1984 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Feydy, Hélène, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Fulenwider, Constance (Morrow), 1980 December 31, 1983 February 2 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Hutchins, Saran (Morgan), 1983 June, 1984 June 17 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Kenney, Edwin, 1983 May 3 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Kenney, Susan (McIlvaine), 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Kenney, Susie, Edwin, Anne and Jamie, Undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Lindbergh, Alika, 1975-1984 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Lindbergh, Anne Spencer, 1970-1985 (Box 2, Folder 48-50)
    - Lindbergh, Annette, 1962 June 16 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Lindbergh, Barbara (Robbins), 1975-1984 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Lindbergh, Erik, Circa 1983-circa 1984 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Lindbergh, Erin, 1981 September 1-November 20 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Lindbergh, Jon, 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Lindbergh, Jon and Barbara (Robbins), 1976 February 19 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Lindbergh, Karen (Pryor), 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Lindbergh, Kristina, 1976-1984 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Lindbergh, Kristina and Conte, Robert, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Lindbergh, Land, 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Lindbergh, Land and Brown, Reeve (Lindbergh), 1975 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Lindbergh, Land, Suzie, Erin, and Peter, 1982 June 25, 1984 July 29 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Lindbergh, Scott, 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 63-64)
    - Lindbergh, Suzie, 1975-1984 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Lindbergh, Wendy, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Morgan, Aubrey Neil, 1982 November 24 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Morgan, Constance (Morrow), 1975-1985 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
    - Morgan, Margaret Eiluned, Circa 1983-circa 1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Morrow, Dwight and Nancy (Lofton), 1976 February 9-April 29 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Morrow, Margot (Loines), 1975-1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Morrow, Nancy (Lofton), 1975-1984 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
    - Morrow, Stephen, 1983 January 14 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Pendleton, Nathaniel, Kim and Connie, 1983 August 24 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Sapieyevski, Jerzy, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Spaeth, Eva Lindbergh Christie, 1976 March 2, 1980 November 7 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Vogel, Gretchen, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Vogel, Heidi, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Vogel, Wendy, 1982 August 15 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Wilkie, Edith, 1981 August 10 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Wilkie, Margot, 1975-1984 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Williams, Faith (Morrow), 1975-1985 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Holiday Cards, Circa 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 19-21)
  - Outgoing correspondence, The series is arranged chronologically.
    The series contains carbon copies of letters written by Lindbergh from 1975 to 1982, with the exception of letters written to her family, which are included in Family correspondence. Includes some incoming correspondence.
    - 1975 (Box 3, Folder 22-25)
    - Circa 1976-circa 1977 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - 1976 January-September (Box 3, Folder 27-29)
    - 1976 October-1977 March (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - 1977 April-1980 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - 1981 (Box 3, Folder 32-34)
    - 1982 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
    - Copies, to friend's after Charles Augustus Lindbergh's death, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
      Includes some incoming correspondence. Original container noted that some letters were removed and included in the diary papers.
    - Ames, Evelyn, Circa 1942-1971 (Box 4, Folder 5-9)
    - Atchley, Dr. Dana, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, Circa 1980-circa 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Writings
    - Diaries, copy, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 12-13)
      Original container was marked "Hold for writing purposes."
    - Journal entries, "Dreams", 1977 February-March (Box 4, Folder 14-15)
    - "Musical Chairs," early drafts, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Personal, medical
    - Correspondence re: dental, Anne Morrow Lindbergh, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Exercises, 1982 September-December (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Article, "Last Things First", 1973 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Lists, notes and receipts, 1974 May-circa 1975 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Material removed from presentation books, Circa 1929-circa 1972, undated (Box 4, Folder 21-22)
    - Stationery, Planorbe, Switzerland, Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Additional material, 1929-1988; 1974-1988; Accession 1989-M-063
  The accession contains correspondence, writings, financial statements, legal documents, printed materials and photographs, primarily from the 1970s and 1980s.
  Legal correspondence, box 13A, is restricted until January 1, 2023 in accordance with donor's request.
  - Correspondence
    - Friends, 1978-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
    - Special friends, 1979-1986 June (Box 1, Folder 6-12)
    - Family, 1979 August-1988 (Box 1, Folder 13-18)
    - Publishers, Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc., 1974-1986 (Box 1, Folder 19-20)
    - General, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - General, 1982-1984 June (Box 2, Folder 1-19)
    - General, 1984 July-1987 June (Box 3, Folder 1-20)
    - General, 1987 July-1988 September (Box 4, Folder 1-5)
    - Readers, 1977-1985 (Box 4, Folder 6-7)
    - Readers, reviews, and correspondence re: Volume V ( War Within and Without ), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 8-10)
    - Outgoing, 1979-1986 June (Box 4, Folder 11-17)
      Consists primarily of carbon copies of outgoing correspondence to friends and family and were originally labeled "diary material," or "only diary kept." A few incoming letters are included.
    - Television programs
      - "60 Minutes" interview, 1980 February-May (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - "Smithsonian World" interview, from friends, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - "Smithsonian World" interview, from fans, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Re: death of Jonathan Lindbergh Brown (grandson), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Greetings Cards
      - Holiday cards, 1982 December-1984 (Box 5, Folder 1-7)
      - Birthday cards, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Requests, 1975-1981 (Box 5, Folder 9-23)
    - Requests, 1983-1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - To be answered ("conscience file"), 1977-1984 (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
    - Pending, 1978 November-1980 April (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Form letter samples, Circa 1950-1973 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Representative mail samples, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Log and instructions, Circa 1981-1986, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Envelopes, separated, 1980, 1985, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Writings by Anne Morrow Lindbergh
    - "Prayer for Peace," Reader's Digest, 1940 January (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - "Relief in Europe" (speech), 1940 December 24 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - "Reaffirmation," Atlantic Monthly, 1941 June (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - "The Most Unforgettable Character I've Met," Reader's Digest, 1947 January (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - "Anywhere in Europe," Harper's Magazine, 1948 April (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - "The Mother and the Child: From the Notebook of Anne Morrow Lindbergh," Harper's Bazaar, 1948 December (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - "Our Lady of Risk," Life, 1950 July 10 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - "Earth Values," The Explorer, 1970 Fall (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Biographical material and drafts of an introduction to the English translation of St. Exupéry's Ecrits de Guerre, 1986, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Writings about Anne Morrow Lindbergh
    - Sutherland, Gretchen Rolufs: Of Winter Branches: The Literary Career of Anne Morrow Lindbergh, 1986 December (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Writings by others
    - Bingham, Alfred M.: Sybil's Bones, a Chronicle of the Three Hiram Binghams, and assorted correspondence, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Boney, H.: poems, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Byard, Margaret M.: "Poetic Responses to the Copernican Revolution", 1977 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Colliton, Margaret: A Case Study in Nursing Thearpy, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Kenney, Edwin J., articles on illness and death, 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Lamont, Corliss: "Steadfast Activist at 84," and additional biographical material, 1981-1986 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Mihailov, Mihailo: "The Mystical Experiences of Loss and Freedom", 1976 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Mitchell, Stephen: The Book of Job: A New Version in English, Undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Mitchell, Stephen: Poems and translations, 1980, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Stirling, Monica: The End of the World Always Happens in the Middle of the Night, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Von Arnim, Achim: "I Searched My Way: The Autobiography of Achim von Arnim, 1881-1940", Undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Quotations and articles saved by Anne Morrow Lindbergh, 1973-1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Things to Read" file, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Topical files
    - Aviation, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Aviation project, Friends' Central School, 1987 February (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Awards and degrees
      - Georgetown University, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Gustavus Adolphus College, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Gustavus Adolphus College, membership, Gustavus Library Associates, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Katherine Wright Memorial Award, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Lanning, Paul, correspondence and photographs, 1976-1982 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Lindbergh, Alika, program for painting exhibition, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Mina Kirstein Curtiss Fund, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 10-12)
    - Smith, Carleton, International Awards Foundation, 1981-1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Smith College, 50th reunion planning, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 2-3)
    - "Smithsonian World" interview, transcripts and correspondence, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Verlhiac Primate Center, Scott and Alika Lindbergh, articles by and about, 1975-1976, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - "Aviation pioneer: Loren Wheeler," notebook, copies of birthday wishes, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, 1929, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Program and note, thesis performance, Frames: A Biographical Portrait of Anne Morrow Lindbergh by Angela Latham-Jones, 1986 May 2 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Videocassette-Thesis performance, Frames: A Biographical Portrait of Anne Morrow Lindbergh by Angela Latham-Jones, 1986 May 2 (Box 14)
  - Financial
    Unless otherwise noted, accounts are owned by Anne Morrow Lindbergh.
    - Correspondence
      - Swiss property, 1962-1967 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Re: burial plot, Charles Augustus Lindbergh, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Re: pre-sale Hana Ranch property, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Contributions and gifts, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 12-14)
      - Children's trusts, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company, 1974-1981 (Box 8, Folder 16-18)
    - Income and capital accounts, Morgan Guaranty Trust Company, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 19-24)
      Includes some statements from the estate of Charles Augustus Lindbergh.
    - Checking accounts
      - Bank of Hawaii, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - Bankers Trust Company, 1974-1981 (Box 8, Folder 26-30)
      - Bankers Trust Company, 1983-1984 January (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
      - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company (Charles Augustus Lindbergh), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company, 1973-1984 January (Box 9, Folder 4-20)
      - Union Trust Company, 1977 December-1978 December (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Union Trust Company, 1978 March-1981 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
    - Savings Account, Morgan Guaranty Trust Company, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Securities accounts
      - Bankers Trust Company, 1974-1981 (Box 12, Folder 4-6)
      - Pictet et Cie, 1970-1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Royalty accounts, multiple publishers, 1975-1981 (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
    - Gift taxes-correspondence and forms, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 10-11)
    - Income taxes - forms, receipts and correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 12-15)
    - Income taxes, estate of Charles Augustus Lindbergh-forms, receipts and correspondence, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Payroll and withholding taxes, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Insurance policies and correspondence, 1975, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 18-19)
  - Housekeeping
    - Bills and receipts, 1974-1981 (Box 12, Folder 20-24)
    - Bills, Argonauta, 1972-1976 (Box 12, Folder 25-28)
    - Reminder lists, inventories and calendars for various properties, 1962, 1971-1974, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Instructions, Scott's Cove house, Undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Expenses, house measurements, and miscellaneous, 1967-1968, 1981, undated (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - Legal
    - Documents-wills, powers of attorney and trusts, 1955, 1962, 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 3-7)
    - Estate of Charles Augustus Lindbergh-letters testamentary, affidavits, inventories and correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 8-13)
      - Restricted (Box 13A)
        Consists of correspondence between Anne Morrow Lindbergh, banks, and attorneys regarding Charles Augustus Lindbergh's bequests to the Hesshaimer and Von Arnim families.
        The materials are closed to research until January 1, 2023 in accordance with the donor's request.
    - Trust-Cutter, Annie E., 1972 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Medical-correspondence re: Anne Morrow Lindbergh, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Art, certificates and awards
    - Program and matted print with stamp, 50th Anniversary of the transatlantic flight, issued by Pan American Airlines, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Program, 56th Anniversary of the transatlantic flight, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Certificate, Anne Morrow Lindbergh, Women of Conscience Award, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Certificate, Anne Morrow Lindbergh, Missouri Historical Society membership, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Booklet, Hill Monastic Library, Collegeville, MN, Undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Print, Garden City Hotel with plane above, signed by the artist, James Feriola, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Print, Morrow Library, Joan Pennington, Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Photograph, Baloon over Sierra Nevada mountains, inscribed to Anne Morrow Lindbergh, Circa 1980 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Photograph, Maui volcano, Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Lithograph, "A Time to Love, a Time to Dream" by Thomas Echternach, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Print, "Charles Augustus Lindbergh," by L. J. Lukfer, signed by the artist, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Print, "Anne Morrow Lindbergh," by L. J. Lukfer, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Print, "Landfall, Dingle Bay, Valentin Island, May 21, 1927," by John T. McCoy, signed by the artist, print # 1/850, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Posters and prints
    - Print, Charles Augustus Lindbergh, 50th Anniversary Commemorative Print, may 20-21, 1927" by Ken Fox, signed by the artist, with print registration certificate, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Poster, "Charles Augustus Lindbergh's Overseas and Overland Flights", Undated (Box 11)
    - Poster, "Lindbergh Heritage Week, May 20-26, 1985" (Box 11)
    - Poster, "After Sixty Five Million Years Quetzalcoatlus Flies Again," inscribed to Anne Morrow Lindbergh from Paul Mac Cready, 11/11/1986 (Box 11)
  - Audiocassette-readings from Gift from the Sea by J. Crawford, 1976 (Box 15)
- Additional material, 1934-1971; Accession 2000-M-117
  The addition consists of copies of popular magazines with articles primarily by Anne Morrow Lindbergh as well as a few by or about Charles Augustus Lindbergh, Jon Lindbergh, and Elizabeth Cutter Morrow (Anne's mother). The titles represented are The Atlantic Monthly, Collier's, Harper's Bazaar, Harper's Magazine, Life, National Geographic, nouveau femina, Reader's Digest, The Saturday Evening Post, This Week Magazine, Women's Home Journal, and Vogue.
  - Published writings, 1934-1971 (Box 1)
- Additional material, 1961-1988; Accession 2002-M-031
  The addition is arranged chronologically.
  The addition consists of diaries. Unless noted otherwise the diaries are original and may include notes, photographs and correspondence.
  - 1961 January-1962 October (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Letter copies
  - 1962 October-1963 Apr, 1963 Aug, 1964 March-May (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Copy of diary, letter copies
  - 1964 May-1964 December (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1965 February-1965 November 26 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1965 November-1966 December (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1967 January-1968 June (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Includes additional diary pages
  - 1968 July-1968 August (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Includes copies of seventy pages
  - 1970 April-1971 February (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 1971 February 12-1972 July (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1982 January-1988 September (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Additional material, 1918-1978; Accession 2002-M-079
  The bulk the accession consists of transcripts of correspondence and writings, the originals of which are filed elsewhere in the collection, and papers related to Anne Morrow Lindbergh's role as executor of her mother's (Elizabeth Cutter Morrow) estate. The accession also includes a helmet and goggles belonging to Anne.
  The accession is arranged into five sections: Correspondence, Writings, Estate of Elizabeth Cutter Morrow, Miscellaneous, and Memorabilia.
  - Correspondence
    - Family
      - Transcripts-original copies, 1921-1941 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Transcripts-original copies, 1931-1933 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Transcripts-third carbons, 1918-1924 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Transcripts-carbons, 1929-1932 (Box 1, Folder 4)